Guide to the Nicole Di Bona Peterson Collection of Advertising Cookbooks, 1850s-2000s
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University, Durham, N.C., USA
- American Cookbooks 1920s, 7
  - Story of Washday, circa 1920s (Box A10, Item 1920sA-0232)
  - 108 Sensible Recipes, 1921 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0001)
    Product: Baker's extracts (i.e. Vanilla, Almond, Celery, etc.)
    Note: Enclosed in a folder with table of measurements, various recipes
  - The Modern Method of Preparing Delightful Foods, 1928 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0002)
    Product: Corn products
    Note: Hard cover, instructions on how to prepare for meals, recipes
  - Cleansing Helps for the Housewife, 1922 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0003)
    Product: Arm & Hammer Washing Soda
    Note: How to use washing soda in the kitchen, laundry, and bathroom
  - Cow Brand Baking Soda is Bicarbonate of Soda and is U.S.P. Standard, circa 1920s (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0004)
    Product: Cow Brand Bicarbonate of Soda
    Note: Writing from a physician on using the product to treat the flu and colds
  - Lesson Plan on Deep Fat Frying, 1929 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0005)
    Product: Davis Baking Powder (unclear)
    Note: Instructions on deep fat frying and recipes for foods to deep fry
  - Royal Cook Book, 1927 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0006)
    Note: Color cover, variety of recipes
  - Rumford Way of Cookery and Household Economy, circa 1920s (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0007)
    Note: Table of measurements, instructions, recipes
  - How to Use the Foods you Can, 1924 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0008)
    Product: Ball jars
    Note: Meals and recipes for each month
  - Sterno Cook Book, 1927 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0009)
    Company: Sterno Corporation
    Product: Sterno canned heat
    Note: Pamphlets and envelope inside containing other Sterno products
  - The Fine Art of Seasoning, 1924 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0010)
    Company: Barton Salt Company
    Product: Barton salt
    Note: History of salt, table appts, table etiquette, valuable uses of salt
  - How to Use Mapleine, circa 1920s (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0011)
    Product: Mapleine
    Note: Very small pamphlet
  - All About Milk, 1923 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0012)
    Note: Some color illustrations (yellow), information and facts about milk
  - Cheese--and Ways to Serve it, 1928 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0013)
    Note: Color illustrations, information and recipes
  - 14 New Gelatin Desserts, 1929 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0014)
    Note: black-and-white and color illustrations
  - Health Value of Knox Sparkling Gelatine, 1924 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0015)
    Note: Health benefits of sparkling gelatine, recipes
  - Jams Jellies and Marmalades made with Certo, 1924 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0016)
    Note: Color illustrations
  - JELL-O America's most famous dessert, 1923 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0017)
    Note: What Jell-O is, a few Jell-O recipes, Norman Rockwell illustrations on front and back
  - Knox Sparkling Granulated Gelatine, 1928 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0018)
    Note: Two recipes on back of small card with color illustrated front
  - Pillsbury's Cook Book, 1924 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0019)
    Note: Background information on the Pillsbury Flour Mills Co., Table of Times, Weights, and Measures
  - Recipes for Globe 'A1' Products, 1923 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0020)
    Company: Globe Grain & Milling Company
    Note: Brief intro, table of weights and measures, deep-fat frying instructions
  - Food and Life Eating for Health, 1926 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0021)
    Note: Written articles, as well as recipes
  - Metropolitan Cook Book, circa 1920s (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0022)
    Note: General rules for various foods and beverages, variety of recipes
  - Whys of Cooking, 1921 (Box B01, Item 1920sB-0023)
    Note: The Story of Crisco, Modern Kitchens, Serving, Various recipes
  - A Few Cooking Suggestions, circa 1920s (Box B02, Item 1920sB-0024)
    Note: Deep-fat frying, pastry making, Cakes, cookies, and quick breads
  - Kingsford's Corn Starch Delightful Desserts, circa 1920s (Box B02, Item 1920sB-0025)
    Company: Corn Products Sales Company
    Product: Kingsford's Cornstarch
    Note: Illustrated cover, six recipes
  - American Waterless Cooker Recipe Book, 1927 (Box B02, Item 1920sB-0026)
    Company: West Bend Company
    Product: American Waterless Cooker
    Note: Color illustrations (orange), advantages, directions, cleaning
  - Frigidaire Frozen Delights, 1929 (Box B02, Item 1920sB-0027)
    Product: Frigidaire-equipped apartments
    Note: Some black-and-white illustrations, proper arrangement of food diagram
  - Salads Suppers Picnics, circa 1920s (Box B02, Item 1920sB-0028)
    Company: Francis H. Leggett & Company
    Product: Premier Salad Dressing
    Note: Salads, Sunday night suppers, dinner dishes, party and chafing dish recipes, picnic and sandwich suggestions
  - Adding Variety to the Menu, 1925 (Box C01, Item 1920sC-0001)
    Note: color illustrations, instruction on how to plan a better meal, offer for free cookbook sent to friends
  - Brand-New Swans Down surprises, circa 1920s (Box C01, Item 1920sC-0002)
  - Cake Secrets, 1926 (Box C01, Item 1920sC-0003)
    Note: color illustrations, swans on cover, free cake set offer inside
  - Fleischmann's Recipes, 1922 (Box C01, Item 1920sC-0004)
    Note: illustrations of children
  - Our Cook Book, circa 1920s (Box C01, Item 1920sC-0006)
    Company: Glen Mills
    Product: Glen Mills Breadstuffs
    Note: fragile condition, illustrative orange cover
  - State Mill and Elevator, 1928 (Box C01, Item 1920sC-0007)
    Company: State Mill and Elevator
    Product: Dakota Maid flour
  - Ward's Cook Book, circa 1920s (Box C01, Item 1920sC-0008)
    Company: Dr. Ward's Medical Company
  - A Selection of Choice Recipes, circa 1920s (Box C01, Item 1920sC-0009)
  - A Selection of Choice Recipes, circa 1920s (Box C01, Item 1920sC-0010)
  - Davis' O.K. Cook Book, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0012)
    Product: Davis' O.K. Baking Powder
    Note: illustrative cover with handwriting, short dialogues giving information throughout book
  - Rumford Dainties and Household Helps, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0013)
  - Golden Key Message, 1928 (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0014)
    Company: Great American Tea Company
    Product: Golden Key Coffee
    Note: fragile condition, foldout pamphlet on hints, recipes, picnic aids, with illustrations
  - Tea- Where it grows How it grows, 1925 (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0015)
    Product: Chase & Sanborn Tea
    Note: story about tea with pictures
  - The Romance of Coffee, 1923 (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0016)
    Product: Chase & Sanborn Coffee
    Note: story about coffee with pictures, handwriting on front cover
  - Twenty Famous Drinks, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0017)
    Company: London Dry Ginger Ale Company, Ltd.
    Product: London Dry
  - Home Desserts and Confections of All Kinds, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0018)
    Product: Hip-O-Lite
  - The Key to Your Locker', circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0019)
    Company: Hansen Office Supply Company
  - Story of Washday… With some of Mrs. S.T. Rorer's copyrighted recipes for preserving Fruits, Jellies, etc., circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0020)
    Company: Standard Oil Corporation
    Product: Parowax
  - 25 Ways to a Man's Heart by a Housewife Who Knows, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0021)
    Company: G. F. Heublein & Brother
    Product: A-1 Steak Sauce
  - Heinz Tomato Products, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0022)
    Product: Heinz Ketchup, Chili Sauce, Tomato Relish
  - Made Dishes Salads and Savories with French's cream salad Mustard, 1925 (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0023)
    Product: French's Cream Salad Mustard
    Note: color illustrations, short note to reader inside
  - Why the Seal? For Safety Demand Ivanhoe the Sealed Mayonnaise, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0024)
    Company: Ivanhoe Foods, Inc.
    Product: Ivanhoe Mayonnaise
  - Healthful Foods, The new method of cooking, 1926 (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0025)
    Product: Wear-Ever Aluminum Cooking Utensils
    Note: 25 cents, colorful illustrations
  - Delicious Suggestions for the Hostess, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0026)
    Company: Sealtest, Inc.
    Product: Hydrox Ice Cream
  - Del Monte Recipes of Flavor, 1923 (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0027)
    Product: Del Monte food products
  - Sunkist Recipes for Every Day, 1928 (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0028)
    Product: Sunkist oranges, lemons
  - Food Economy: Recipes for Left-Overs, Plain Desserts and Salads, by Mrs. Knox, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0029)
    Product: Sparkling Gelatine
  - Jell-O Girl Entertains, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0030)
  - Recipes for Tempting Dishes using Jams and Jellies, 1929 (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0031)
    Company: Certo Corporation
    Product: Certo for use in making Jams & Jellies
    Note: color illustrations, note to reader on inside cover
  - Crisp and Tasty! Triscuit the Shredded Wheat Cracker, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0033)
    Product: Triscuit Crackers
    Note: color illustration on cover and back
  - Fifty Ways of Serving Shredded Wheat, 1924 (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0034)
    Note: color illustrations on cover and back
  - Health, Growth and Happiness for Boys and Girls, 1924 (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0035)
    Product: Ralston Whole Wheat Cereal and Flour
    Note: color illustrations, descriptive charts
  - The Metropolitan Cook Book, 1927 (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0036)
    Product: Cookbook
    Note: front cover slightly torn, black-and-white illustration on front and back
  - 8 New Appetizing Ham Recipes Using Luer's Hickory Smoked Ham, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0037)
    Company: Luer Packing Company, Inc.
    Product: Luer's Ham
  - Try These 4 Scrapple Recipes, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0038)
    Company: F. G. Vogt & Son, Inc.
    Product: Vogt's Scrapple
  - Come into the Kitchen, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0039)
    Product: Lydia Pinkham Medicines
    Note: fragile condition, cover torn and loose, inside recipes and suggestions for health, offer for free text book
  - First National Bank Notes, 1920 (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0040)
    Company: First National Bank
    Product: The First National Bank, South Boston, VA
    Note: black-and-white illustrations, short stories about saving
  - Home Dressmaking, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0041)
    Note: information/diagrams of sewing techniques, offer for free sewing card combo, illustrations on cover and back
  - Armour's 'STAR' Dry Sausage, Armour's Veribest MILK Recipes, Just a few Armour's STAR Bacon Recipes, Armour's 'SIMON PURE' 100% Leaf Lard Recipes, Armour's Vegetole for Cooking, Baking, Frying, Armour's Cloverbloom pasteurized-blended Cheese, Recipes for Using Armour's Star Pure Lard, Some of the 60 ways to serve Armour's Star Ham, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0042)
    Product: Armour's star sausage, veribest evaporated milk, star bacon, Simon pure leaf lard, vegetable, clover bloom cheese, star pure lard, star ham
    Note: set of 8 two page pamphlets with color illustrations advertising Armour's products
  - Corn Products Cook Book, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0043)
    Product: Karo Corn Syrup, Kingsford Corn Starch
  - Corn Products Cook Book, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0044)
    Note: color illustration inserts, illustrations on front and back
  - Peanut Dishes and How To Prepare Them, 1920 (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0045)
    Company: Eastern Peanut Company
    Product: Pride O'Perquimans Peanuts
    Note: small black-and-white illustrations
  - Tested Recipes and Premium Catalog, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0046)
    Company: B. S. Pearsall Butter Company
    Product: Elgin Nut Margarine
  - When Old Virginia Came to Meals, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0047)
    Company: Pancrust-Plato Company
    Product: Pancrust Shortening
  - Waffles Baked in a Modernized Iron, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0048)
    Company: Fitzgerald Manufacturing Company
    Product: STAR-Rite Empress Waffle Iron
  - Heinz Mandalay Sauce A Treat from the Orient, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0049)
    Product: Heinz Mandalay Sauce
  - for Home Candy Making, Karo The Great American Syrup for Every Purpose, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0050)
    Company: Karo Syrup
    Product: Karo Syrup
  - Mapleine Dainties--how to make them, circa 1920s (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0051)
  - New Sauerkraut Salad Recipes, circa 1924 (Box C02, Item 1920sC-0052)
    Company: National Kraut Packers Association
    Product: sauerkraut
    Note: Recipe card stored with envelope and letter from National Kraut Packers Assn. to Josephine Nemmich
  - Baker's Coconut Recipes, 1923 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0001)
  - Light Fare Recipes for Corn Flour and Paisley Flour Cookery, 1920 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0002)
    Company: Brown & Polson
    Product: Brown and Polson corn flour
    Note: C. Herman Senn
  - Cake Secrets, 1926 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0003)
    Note: Mary Jean Hart
  - The Swans Down way of perfect cakes, 1927 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0004)
  - Spices of the Orient, 1927 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0005)
    Product: Watkins spices and extracts
    Note: Historical representations
  - Ralston Recipes, 1923 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0006)
    Product: Purina flours
  - What Every Woman Should Know About Baking, 1926 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0007)
    Company: Washburn Crosby Company
    Note: Betty Crocker
  - A Monograph on Muffins, 1923 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0008)
    Note: Helen Harrington Downing
  - Reliable Recipes, circa 1920s (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0009)
  - Clabber Girl Baking Book, circa 1920s (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0010)
    Company: Hulman and Company
    Product: Clabber Girl baking powder
  - Rumford Cookbook, 1920 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0011)
  - Rumford Home Recipes, circa 1920s (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0012)
    Note: Fannie Merritt Farmer, Lily Haxworth Wallace, Mildred Maddocks
  - The Rumford Way of Cookery and Household Economy, 1920 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0013)
    Note: Janet McKenzie Hill
  - Hip-o-Lite The Book of Caterers and Chefs Professional recipes, 1922 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0014)
  - Auto Vacuum Frozen Dainties, 1922-1924 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0015)
    Product: Auto Vacuum Freezers
  - Choice Recipes, 1923 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0016)
    Note: Miss Maria Parloa, Janet McKenzie Hill
  - Famous Recipes for Baker's Chocolate and Breakfast Cocoa, 1928 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0017)
  - The Salad Bowl, 1929 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0018)
    Product: Best Foods mayonnaise
  - The Book of Salads, circa 1920s (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0019)
    Product: King Taste dressings
  - Better Cooking Kitchen Craft Waterless Cooker Recipe Book, 1925 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0020)
    Company: Kitchen Craft Company (Div. of West Bend)
    Product: Kitchen Craft waterless cooker
  - Borden's Eagle Brand Book of Recipes, circa 1920s (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0021)
    Company: Borden Condensed Milk Company
  - Frozen Foods, 1929 (Box D03, Item 1920sD-0022)
  - Cheese-And Ways to Serve It, 1928 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0023)
  - The Kingdom that Grew Out of a Little Boy's Garden, 1927 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0024)
    Product: Dole Hawaiian pineapple
    Note: Marion Mason Hale
  - Home Made Banana Recipes, 1929 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0025)
    Company: Standard Fruit Company
    Product: Bananas
  - Recipes with Raisins, 1923 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0026)
    Note: Mrs. Bell de Graf
  - Knox Gelatine A Delicious Food of Superior Quality, 1929 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0027)
  - Jell-O Recipes, 1925 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0028)
  - What you can do with Jell-O, 1928 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0029)
  - Jell-O Desserts for Special Occasions, 1927 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0030)
  - 50 Ways of Serving Cream of Wheat, 1924 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0031)
    Note: African American Cook featured on the cover
  - A Hundred Ways to Serve Herman's Dutch Tea Rusk, 1929 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0032)
    Company: Dutch Tea Rusk Co
    Product: Herman's Dutch Tea Rusk
  - How to use-Taystee Bread, 1929 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0033)
    Note: Agnes Carroll Hayward
  - The Florence Cook Book, circa 1920s (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0034)
    Company: Central Oil & Gas Stove Company
    Product: Florence Oil Cook Stove
  - The New Perfection Cook Book, 1923 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0035)
    Product: Perfection Oil Cook Stove
  - Estate Cook Book, 1924 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0036)
    Product: Estate gas range
  - Electric Refrigerator Menus and Recipes, 1927 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0037)
    Note: Miss Alice Bradley
  - The Wilcolator Cook Book, 1925-1930 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0038)
  - Enjoy these Menus and Recipes, circa 1920s (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0039)
    Company: Peters Products
    Product: Peters sausages
  - A Collation of Cakes Yesterday and Today, 1923 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0040)
    Note: Claudia Quigley Murphy, includes brief historical essay on cake recipes
  - What to Serve and How to Serve It, 1927 (Box D04, Item 1920sD-0041)
    Company: International Silver Co
    Product: Silverware
  - Watkins Cook Book, 1925 (Box D05, Item 1920sD-0042)
    Product: Miscellaneous Watkins products
  - Secrets in Cooking, circa 1920s (Box D05, Item 1920sD-0043)
    Company: Ladies' Auxiliary, Sons of Veterans
    Note: includes 'How to Cook a Husband'
  - Delightful Cooking with the Three Great Products from Corn, circa 1920s (Box D05, Item 1920sD-0044)
    Product: Karo syrup, Argo corn starch, Mazola oil, Linit starch
  - One Hundred Delights, 1922 (Box D05, Item 1920sD-0045)
    Product: Dromedary products
  - Rawleigh's Good Health Guide and Cookbook, 1928 (Box D05, Item 1920sD-0046)
    Product: Rawleigh's Good Health Products
  - Mazola Recipes, circa 1920s (Box D05, Item 1920sD-0047)
  - The Modern Method of Preparing Delightful Foods, 1926 (Box D05, Item 1920sD-0048)
    Note: Ida Bailey Allen, features a Native American on the cover
  - Recipes Jelke Goodluck Margarine, 1927 (Box D05, Item 1920sD-0049)
    Product: Good Luck margarine
  - Eagle Cook Book, 1922 (Box OV B01, Item OZ 1920sB-0001)
    Company: Published by the Brooklyn Daily Eagle
    Note: black-and-white photographs and drawings, color ad for Maxwell House on inside cover, multiple ads, weekly expenditure chart
  - Short Cuts to the Dinner Table by Vera A. Schneider, circa 1920s (Box OV B01, Item OZ 1920sB-0002)
    Company: Multiple (supplement to Daily Local News, West Chester, PA)
    Note: black-and-white photographs and drawings in ads for multiple products, black-and-white drawings on top of recipe pages
  - Electric Cookery by Hotpoint, circa 1920s (Box OV B01, Item OZ 1920sB-0003)
    Company: Edison General Electric Appliance Company
    Product: Hotpoint ovens
    Note: black-and-white photographs (lots of demonstration photographs ), How to cook in a Hotpoint oven
  - Any one can Bake!, 1927 (Box OV C01, Item OZ 1920sC-0001)
    Note: color illustrations, black-and-white descriptive pictures, short sections of useful information.
  - Pillsbury's Cook Book, 1921 (Box OV C01, Item OZ 1920sC-0002)
    Product: Pillsbury's Best Flour
    Note: Oversize, color picture of Pillsbury mill, includes sheet with handwritten recipe not in English
  - You'll Like Mrs. F.W. McNess' Tested Cocoa Recipes, circa 1920s (Box OV C01, Item OZ 1920sC-0003)
    Product: McNess Cocoa, McNess Vanilla, McNess Cinnamon, McNess Ginger
    Note: Oversize, black-and-white illustrations
  - A Cook Book for the Modern Home Maker Showing the Value of Using More Milk in the Menu, 1928 (Box OV C01, Item OZ 1920sC-0004)
    Company: Mathews Industries, Inc.
  - Royal Summer-time Recipes, circa 1920s (Box OV C01, Item OZ 1920sC-0005)
  - The AutomatiCook Book, 1927 (Box OV C01, Item OZ 1920sC-0006)
    Company: RobertShaw Thermostat Company
    Product: Wedgewood Ranges
    Note: tips on canning
  - Home Digest… The Battle Creek Health Foods Magazine, 1929 (Box OV C01, Item OZ 1920sC-0007)
    Product: Health foods
    Note: color and black-and-white photographs and illustrations
- American Cookbooks 1930s, 8
  - Beer Party: Tempting Recipes and Jacob Ruppert Beer, 1937 (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0001)
    Category: Alcoholic Beverages
    Company: Jacob Ruppert Brewery
    Product: Jacob Ruppert Beer
    Note: Menu suggestions
  - Cooking with Wine Recipes, 1935 (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0002)
    Company: Roma Wine Company
    Product: Roma wines
    Note: Spokeswoman: Mona Van Dyke. Production: photographs of wine factory
  - Easy Ways to Cook with Wine, 1939 (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0003)
    Company: Wine Advisory Board
    Product: Wine
    Note: Compliments of Mulroy's Liquor & Wine Store, Syracuse NY
  - Fun at Cocktail Time, 1934 (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0004)
    Company: Seagram-Distillers Corporation
    Product: Seagram's Bourbon, Gin, V.O.
    Note: Includes pictures of distilleries
  - Irvin S. Cobb's Own Recipe Book, 1934 (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0005)
    Company: Frankfort Distillers Corporation
    Product: Four Roses or Paul Jones whiskey
    Note: Appeal to romanticized past, American history. Cover illustration of two pioneer men, quote by Abraham Lincoln. Inside, illustrations of antebellum South (some racial content)
  - Latest Edition of the Original Merry Mixer, 1936 (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0006)
    Company: Schenley Products Company, Inc.
    Product: Schenley liquors, Assorted: Bacardi, Kintore, Noilly Prat, Otard, Silver Wedding, Castledor, Bardinet, Dubonnet, vermouth, gin, curacao, rum, champagne, whiskey, wine, cognac
    Note: Note on temperance and drinking in moderation at beginning.
  - Life of the Party (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0007)
    Company: Three Feathers Distributers
    Product: Three Feathers Whiskey
    Note: Includes musical arrangements for quartets
  - Sunday Evenings, 1934 (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0008)
    Product: Ruppert's Beer
    Note: Recipes to be served as Sunday dinners, accompanied by beer
  - Wilken Family Home Cooking Album, 1935 (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0009)
    Company: Jos. S. Finch & Company
    Product: Wilken Family Whisky
  - 15 Ways to a Man's Heart, 1933 (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0010)
    Company: General Mills, Inc.
    Product: Gold Medal Cake Flour
    Note: Foreword from Betty Crocker, 2nd Edition
  - 9 New Helps for Meal Planners, 1936 (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0011)
  - Angostura: Famous for Foods, 1934 (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0012)
    Company: Angostura-Wuppermann Corporation
    Product: Angostura Bitters
    Note: Detached cove: color cover of woman cooking
  - Bake Day Suggestions, circa 1930s (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0013)
  - Balanced Recipes, 1933 (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0014)
    Product: Pillsbury flour, wheat bran, corn meal, farina, etc.
    Note: black-and-white picture of test kitchen, bound in metal case
  - Betty Crocker's 101 Delicious Bisquick Creations, 1933 (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0015)
    Product: Bisquick
  - Betty Crocker's 15 Prize Recipes: Favorites of Each Year – 1921 to 1936, 1936-1937 (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0016)
    Product: Gold Medal 'Kitchen-tested' Flour
  - Ceresota Household Hints, Series 2, circa 1930s (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0017)
    Company: Ceresota
    Product: Ceresota Unbleached Flour
  - Finest Flour Money Can Buy', circa 1930s (Box 1930s-1, Item 1930s-0018)
    Company: J. Allen Smith & Company
    Product: White Lily flour
    Note: Missing both covers, first 6 pages, and possibly pages at the end
  - Gold Medal Sandwich Book, circa 1930s (Box 1930s-2, Item 1930s-0019)
    Note: Compliment of Watkins Store, Ilion, NY
  - Good Luck Recipes, 1939 (Box 1930s-2, Item 1930s-0020)
    Note: Small pamphlet with six recipes
  - Good Things to Eat, 1936 (Box 1930s-2, Item 1930s-0021)
    Product: Arm & Hammer and Cow Brand baking sodas
    Note: Spokesperson: Martha Lee Anderson, 114th edition
  - Good Things to Eat, 1938 (Box 1930s-2, Item 1930s-0022)
    Note: Spokesperson: Martha Lee Anderson